sexlikereal.com 2019-05-30

# VR Porn Movies for Cardboard, GearVR, Oculus | SexLikeReal

## Privacy Policy

Pursuant to our Terms of Use, this document describes how we treat personal information related to your use of the Website, including information you provide when using it.

We expressly and strictly limit use of the Website to adults over 18 years of age or the age of majority in the individual’s jurisdiction, whichever is greater. Anyone under this age is strictly forbidden from using the Website. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained this age.

### Data Collected

##### Browsing the Website

You can use the search function, view articles, videos and pictures, and access other parts of the Website without having an account, in which case only your IP address, country of origin and other information about your computer or device (such as web requests, device type, browser type, browser language, referring URL, operating system and date and time of requests) will be recorded for log file information, aggregated traffic information and in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content. If you have an account on the website and are logged in, the information may be associated with your account.

##### Registering on the Website

Registration of an account is required for using many parts of the Website, including purchasing access to certain content and using many other features. We request additional information at the time of your registration, including, without limitation, your name, email address and a password. Your IP address is recorded automatically. We may ask for further information to fill out your profile details. Some of this information may be used to provide you the Website and may become publicly available through your profile or through other use of the Website. If you intend to make your content available on the Website, we will collect additional information necessary to confirm your authority, confirm your compliance with law and to make available where necessary on the Website for others.

##### Usage Information

We may record information about your usage of the Website such as pageviews, clicks, mousemoves, duration of video views, portions of videos viewed, search phrases, referrers and other various statistics. If you have registered and are logged in, we may associate that information with your account.

##### Uploaded Content

Any personal information or content you voluntarily publicly disclose online, including animations, pictures, videos, comments and your profile page or any other User Submissions, becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others.

##### Other Information

You may have the ability to make comments on content and engage in other social activities. Any such activities may be visible to the public.

##### Correspondences

We may keep a record of any correspondence between you and us.

##### Cookies

When you use the Website, we may send cookies to your computer to uniquely identify your browser session. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies.

##### Payment Information

If you provide us payment information we will keep this in our system for the purposes of taking payments from you or making payments to you as appropriate. This information may also be provided to our third party payment processors and affiliates in order to assist with the taking or making of payments. Credit cards, debit cards or bank account information are not stored by our website, but third party payment processors.

### Data Usage

We may use your information to provide you with certain features and to create a personalized experience on the Website. We may also use that information to operate, maintain and improve features and functionality of the Website, including building a recommendation system for the Website.

We may use your e-mail address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages. We may use your e-mail for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

We use cookies, web beacons and other information to store information so that you will not have to re-enter it on future visits, provide personalized content and information, monitor the effectiveness of the Website and monitor aggregate metrics such as the number of visitors and page views (including for use in monitoring visitors from affiliates). They may also be used to provide targeted advertising based on your country of origin and other personal information.

We may aggregate your personal information with personal information of other members and users, and disclose such information to advertisers and other third-parties for marketing and promotional purposes.

Your username may be displayed to other visitors of the Website alongside content on the Website in relation to your uploaded content and other similar features.

We may use your information to run promotions, contests, surveys and other features and events.

### Disclosures of Information

We may be required to release certain data to comply with legal obligations or in order to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. We may also release certain data to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users and others. This includes providing information to other companies or organizations like the police or governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against or prosecution of any illegal activity, whether or not it is identified in the Terms of Use.

If you upload any illegal or unauthorized material to the Website, or you are suspected of doing such, we may forward all available information to relevant authorities, including respective copyright owners, without any notice to you.

We may also share your information with third parties for the purposes of payment processing and any such information will also be subject to their privacy policies.

### Miscellaneous

If you have an account on the Website and have a password giving you access to certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping the password confidential. Anyone else with your password may access your account and other personal information.

While we use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to secure your information, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information or content you transmit to us. Any information or content you transmit to us is done at your own risk.
